Willard Eugene Hotchkiss Arbitration Awards and Papers 5238
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  Painters' Furlough, Meadville Plant, May 19
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  Rate of Pay on new Spinning Machine at Front Royal, May 29
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  Eligibility of Laboratory Employees, Front Royal, June 14
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  Clarification of Pronouncements Concerning Scheduling, July 20
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, Front Royal Cases, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  1. Drain Case Promotion, 2. Motor Winders Rate for 8 men, 3. E. J. Hallowell Suspension Case, 4. Oiling Trucks, 5. Demotion of David Lee, Welder, August 22
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, Front Royal - In re Carpenter Lay Off, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  Aug. 22nd
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  Stoppage Cases - Payne-Rieve Letters, September 11
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  Borden Wines Case, Front Royal Plant, September 13
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  Sunday Maintenance Work, Roanoke, September 18
- American Viscose Corporation arid Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  In re Rates for Oilers, Tire Fabric Dept., Roanoke Plant, September 22
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  1. In re rates for Belt Thread Machine Operators, opugh Grinders, etc., Roanoke, 2. In re Procurement Department Specialists, Roanoke, October 25
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  In re discipline for not reporting for work April 8 and 9, Parkersburg Plant, Electrical Department, November 13
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  Blessing Case, Lewistown, Decision, March 20
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  Roland Walker and Vera Warren, Dismissal Wage, Marcus Hook Plant, March 20
- American Viscose Corporation and Textile Workers Union of America, 1944-1945 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  Cases heard December 28, 1944, Record of Status - Jack Hammer Case, Decisions January 22, 1945 and March 31, 1945
- Restaurant and Hotel Employers' Council of Southern California and Los Angeles Local Joint Executive Board, Culinary Workers and Bartenders, A. F. L, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  Sept. 12th